BU Records: Office of the President (Abner Vernon McCall), Inclusive: 1845-1981, undated, Bulk: 1961-1981
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- External, 1936-1981, undated; 3
  - Heart O’Texas Lions Club, 1968-1978 (Box 120, Folder 25)
  - Heart O’Texas Parade, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - Heart O’Texas Study of American Heritage, 1974-1981 (Box 120, Folder 27)
  - Henderson Independent School District, 1972 (Box 120, Folder 28)
  - Herbert Hoover Presidential Library, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 29)
  - Heritage Insurance Managers, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 30)
  - Higher Education Facilities Act, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Hillcrest Baptist Hospital, 1964-1978 (Box 120, Folder 32)
  - Hispanic Baptist Centennial History, 1981 (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - Historical Committee of the Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1971 (Box 120, Folder 34)
  - Hoblitzelle Foundation, 1970-1975 (Box 120, Folder 35)
  - Hogg Foundation, 1960-1967 (Box 120, Folder 36)
  - Holiday Inn, 1975-1976 (Box 120, Folder 37)
  - Home Mission Board, 1962-1978 (Box 120, Folder 38)
  - Honeywell, Inc., 1967-1970 (Box 120, Folder 39)
  - Hong Kong Baptist College (Baylor in Asia), 1960-1963 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Hong Kong Baptist College (Baylor in Asia), 1966-1978 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Hooker Construction Company, 1962-1975 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Horatio Alger Awards Committee, 1963-1980 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Hosei University, 1978-1979 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - House of Poetry, 1972-1974 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - House Rules 9096, 1961 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Household Finance Corporation, 1962-1975 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Houston Baptist University, 1960-1978 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Houston Baylor Club, 1965-1975 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Houston Chronicle, 1961-1972 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Houston Endowment, Inc., 1971-1979 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Houston Post, 1963-1972 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Howard College, 1963 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Howard Payne University, 1967-1981 (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - Humble Oil and Refining Company, 1962-1972 (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - Hyde Park Baptist Church, 1967-1981 (Box 121, Folder 17)
  - I Cross-Reference Sheets, 1963-1977 (Box 121, Folder 18)
  - “Ideal Miss” Pageant, 1972-1974 (Box 121, Folder 19)
  - Illinois State University, 1976 (Box 121, Folder 20)
  - Improved Order of Red Men, 1967 (Box 121, Folder 21)
  - Independence Campus, 1957-1976 (Box 121, Folder 22)
  - Independent College Funds of America, Inc., 1964-1979 (Box 121, Folder 23)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT), 1965-1968 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (1 of 2), 1969 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (1 of 3), 1970 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (2 of 3), 1970 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (3 of 3), 1970 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (1 of 3), 1971 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (2 of 3), 1971 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (3 of 3), 1971 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (1 of 2), 1972 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (2 of 2), 1972 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT), 1975 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT), 1977 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT), 1978 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT)/Ford Foundation Study, 1978 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) — Research Foundation, 1976-1981 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) — Senate Bill 56 (1 of 3), 1971 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) — Senate Bill 56 (2 of 3), 1971 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) — Senate Bill 56 (3 of 3), 1971 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Independent Senior Colleges and Universities in Texas, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Institute for College and University Administrators, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Institute for the Humanities at Salado, 1980-1981 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Institute for Research in Childhood Learning Disorders, 1979-1981 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Institute for the Study of the Interaction of Foreign and Domestic Affairs, 1977-1981 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Institute of International Education, 1961-1976 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Institute of Labor Policy and Analysis, 1978-1980 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Institute of Latin American Studies, 1974 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Institute of Professional Accountancy, 1976 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Institution Boards, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Institution Study Committee, circa 1972 (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - Instituto Technológico y de Estudios Superiores de Monterrey, 1963-1967 (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - Insurance Graphic, 1961 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Inter-Agency Committee on Mexican American Affairs, 1968-1969 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Inter-Agency Conference, 1976 (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1960-1977 (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - International Association of Universities, 1975-1980 (Box 126, Folder 17)
  - International Business Machines (IBM), 1959-1980 (Box 126, Folder 18)
  - International City Managers’ Association, 1967-1968 (Box 126, Folder 19)
  - International Summer School, 1964 (Box 126, Folder 20)
  - The International Supreme Council Order of DeMolay, 1960-1968 (Box 126, Folder 21)
  - Interuniversity Communications Council, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 22)
  - Iredell Public Schools, 1965 (Box 126, Folder 23)
  - Israel Information Center, 1973 (Box 126, Folder 24)
  - J Cross-Reference Sheets, 1968-1978 (Box 126, Folder 25)
  - James Connally Technical Institute, 1966 (Box 126, Folder 26)
  - Jeff Hamilton Historical Committee, 1976 (Box 126, Folder 27)
  - Jewish Publication Society of America, 1977-1979 (Box 126, Folder 28)
  - Jewish Welfare Council of Waco and Central Texas, 1974 (Box 126, Folder 29)
  - Jobs for Texans, 1978 (Box 126, Folder 30)
  - John Deere Company, 1963-1974 (Box 126, Folder 31)
  - John Price Jones Company, 1959-1960 (Box 126, Folder 32)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1970 (Box 126, Folder 33)
  - Johns-Manville Sales Corporation, 1965-1969 (Box 126, Folder 34)
  - Joseph and Helen Davidson Charitable Foundation, 1969 (Box 126, Folder 35)
  - Judson College, 1972-1974 (Box 126, Folder 36)
  - Junior College Material, 1963-1971 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - K Cross-Reference Sheets, 1967-1973 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Kansas State University, 1969 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Kappa Alpha Order, 1976 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma, 1977 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Kappa Kappa Psi, 1962 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Kayser Foundation, 1974-1976 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - KAWA, 1964-1973 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - KBOX Radio, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - KCEN-TV, 1966-1968 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Kent State University, 1971 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Kerr-McGee Merit Scholar, 1964 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Key Club International, 1963 (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - Kilgore College, 1969 (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - Kiwanis Club, 1964-1980 (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - Knights Templar, 1967 (Box 127, Folder 16)
  - Knox Foundation, 1973-1977 (Box 127, Folder 17)
  - Kowloon Baptist Church, 1972 (Box 127, Folder 18)
  - Kresge Foundation, 1965-1975 (Box 127, Folder 19)
  - KWTX, 1961-1976 (Box 127, Folder 20)
  - L Cross-Reference Sheets, 1961-1978 (Box 127, Folder 21)
  - Lakeside Baptist Church, 1980 (Box 127, Folder 22)
  - Lamar University, 1979-1980 (Box 127, Folder 23)
  - Latin American Scholarships, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 24)
  - Law Enforcement, 1966-1978 (Box 127, Folder 25)
  - League of Women Voters of Texas, 1961-1972 (Box 127, Folder 26)
  - Legal Aid Clinic, 1960 (Box 127, Folder 27)
  - Legislation Advisory Committee, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 28)
  - Liaison Committee on Texas Private College and Universities, 1963-1968 (Box 127, Folder 29)
  - Libertad Chapter of the Daughters of the American Revolution, 1978 (Box 127, Folder 30)
  - Liberty Baptist College, 1978 (Box 127, Folder 31)
  - Library of Congress, 1972-1978 (Box 127, Folder 32)
  - Lincoln Park Presbyterian Church, 1976 (Box 127, Folder 33)
  - Little League, 1975-1987 (Box 127, Folder 34)
  - Liquor Legislation (1 of 4), 1967-1969 (Box 127, Folder 35)
  - Liquor Legislation (2 of 4), 1967-1969 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Liquor Legislation (3 of 4), 1967-1969 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Liquor Legislation (4 of 4), 1967-1969 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Loan Shark Committee, 1958 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Loan Shark Committee (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Loan Shark Committee (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Lone Star Gas Company, 1964-1969 (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Loomis Sayles and Company, 1966 (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Loomis Sayles and Company, 1967 (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Loomis Sayles and Company, 1968-1971 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - L.A. Pires York Rite Scholarship Fund, 1975 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Louisiana Baptist Convention, 1977 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Louisiana College, 1979-1978 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Louisiana State University, 1959 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Louisiana Tech University, 1974 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Lowich Brothers (Hill Building), 1946-1958 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Lubbock Baptist Association, 1961 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Lubbock Chamber of Commerce, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Lubrizol Foundation, 1974-1975 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Luther Rice College, 1974-1976 (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Lutheran Student Assistance Fund/Scholarships, 1965 (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - M Cross-Reference Sheets, 1959-1978 (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - Mabee Foundation, 1966-1978 (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - Main Lafrentz Company, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - Manchaca Baptist Church, 1969 (Box 129, Folder 16)
  - Manpower Planning Committee, 1974 (Box 129, Folder 17)
  - Marathon Oil Company, 1966-1974 (Box 129, Folder 18)
  - Marine Corps Recruiting, 1971-1975 (Box 129, Folder 19)
  - Mars Hill College, 1980 (Box 129, Folder 20)
  - Maryland Baptist College, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 21)
  - Masonic Home, 1962-1973 (Box 129, Folder 22)
  - Masonic Independent School District, 1967-1975 (Box 129, Folder 23)
  - Masonic Lodge, 1959-1970 (Box 129, Folder 24)
  - Masons, 1961-1963 (Box 129, Folder 25)
  - Mayor and City Council of Waco, 1970 (Box 129, Folder 26)
  - McGrath Study, 1976-1977 (Box 129, Folder 27)
  - McLachlan Scholarship Fund, 1961-1962 (Box 129, Folder 28)
  - McLennan Community College, 1966-1969 (Box 129, Folder 29)
  - McMurry College, 1970 (Box 129, Folder 30)
  - Medical Education, 1962-1967 (Box 129, Folder 31)
  - Medical Research Foundation, 1959-1960 (Box 129, Folder 32)
  - Meir International Study League, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 33)
  - Memphis Baylor Club, 1976 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Memphis State University, 1975 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Mental Health-Mental Retardation Center, 1966-1969 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Mercer University, 1962-1980 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Metalab Equipment Company, 1963-1964 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Methodist Home, 1963-1973 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Methodist Hospital, 1967-1978 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Methodist Student Center, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Methodist Student Movement of Texas, Inc., 1963 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, 1974-1977 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Mid-South Magazine Agency, Inc., 1967 (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Mid-Tex Association, 1961-1963 (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Midwestern Baptist Theological Seminary, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 13)
  - Midwestern University, 1969-1970 (Box 130, Folder 14)
  - Migrant Education Task Force, 1977 (Box 130, Folder 15)
  - Minimum Wage Bill, 1973 (Box 130, Folder 16)
  - Ministerial Alliance, 1968 (Box 130, Folder 17)
  - Minister’s Day, 1962 (Box 130, Folder 18)
  - Minnie Stevens Piper Foundation, 1962-1972 (Box 130, Folder 19)
  - Miss Texas Pageant, 1980 (Box 130, Folder 20)
  - Mississippi College, 1965-1981 (Box 130, Folder 21)
  - Mississippi State University, 1977-1980 (Box 130, Folder 22)
  - Missouri Southern State College, 1979 (Box 130, Folder 23)
  - Mobil Chemical Company, 1968-1971 (Box 130, Folder 24)
  - Mobile College, 1963-1976 (Box 130, Folder 25)
  - Model Cities Program, 1967-1970 (Box 130, Folder 26)
  - Modern Language Association, 1960 (Box 130, Folder 27)
  - Moor Children’s Home, 1969-1970 (Box 130, Folder 28)
  - Mormons, 1980-1981 (Box 130, Folder 29)
  - Morrison Estate and Trust, 1959-1970 (Box 130, Folder 30)
  - N Cross-Reference Sheets, 1967-1978 (Box 130, Folder 31)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), 1962-1979 (Box 130, Folder 32)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1962-1966 (Box 130, Folder 33)
  - National Accounting Fraternity [Beta Alpha Psi], 1974 (Box 130, Folder 34)
  - National Accreditation Council, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 35)
  - National Association of College and University Attorneys, 1977 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - National Association of College and University Business Officers, 1971-1973 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities (NAICU), 1976-1978 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities (NAICU), 1979-1980 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1974-1980 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - National Beta Club, 1962-1981 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - National Center for Higher Education, 1973 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - National Church Data Systems, Inc., 1969 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - National Civil Service League, 1963 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 1959-1963 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 1966-1974 (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 1975-1978 (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 1979-1981 (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association — Committee on Recruiting and Financial Aid, 1960 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - National Commission for Cooperative Education, 1978 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - National Commission on Accrediting, 1962-1974 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1964 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - National Conference of Religious and Lay Leaders, 1979 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - National Congress on Church-Related Colleges and Universities, 1979 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - National Council for Social Studies, 1965 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - National Council of Catholic Men, 1961 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - National Council of Churches, 1969 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - National Council of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1972-1974 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - National Council of the Young Men’s Christian Associations, 1962 (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - National Council on Legal Clinics, 1962 (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - National Defense Education Act, 1961-1966 (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - National Fellowship on Christian Schools, 1979 (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - National Football Clinic, 1964 (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - National Football Foundation, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 16)
  - National Foundation, 1961 (Box 132, Folder 17)
  - National Fraternities, 1969, undated (Box 132, Folder 18)
  - National Health Council, 1975 (Box 132, Folder 19)
  - National Intramural Association, 1963 (Box 132, Folder 20)
  - National Institute of General Medical Sciences, 1963 (Box 132, Folder 21)
  - National Institute of Health, 1965 (Box 132, Folder 22)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc., 1964-1972 (Box 132, Folder 23)
  - National Merit Scholarship Corporation, 1962-1975 (Box 132, Folder 34)
  - National Research Council, 1964-1980 (Box 132, Folder 25)
  - National Science Foundation, 1960-1962 (Box 132, Folder 26)
  - National Science Foundation, 1963-1964 (Box 132, Folder 27)
  - National Science Foundation, 1965 (Box 132, Folder 28)
  - National Science Foundation, 1966 (Box 132, Folder 29)
  - National Science Foundation, 1967 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - National Science Foundation, 1968 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - National Science Foundation, 1969-1976 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - National Students Association, 1971 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - National Student Symposium on the Presidency, 1973 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - National University Extension Association, 1980 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - National Western Life Insurance Company, 1965 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Nature Conservancy, 1974 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Navarro Junior College, 1963-1973 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Near East Foundation, 1962 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - New American Patriots, 1980 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - New Mexico State University, 1964 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - New Orleans Baptist Theological Seminary, 1962-1975 (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - New York Times Guide to Colleges — Questionnaire for Presidents, circa 1980 (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - Nominating Board Committee [Waco], 1967 (Box 133, Folder 15)
  - Non-Public School Education, 1970 (Box 133, Folder 16)
  - North American Aviation, Inc., 1963 (Box 133, Folder 17)
  - North American Baptist Fellowship, 1975-1980 (Box 133, Folder 18)
  - North Texas State University, 1965-1980 (Box 133, Folder 19)
  - O Cross Reference Sheets, 1962-1976 (Box 133, Folder 20)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities, 1978-1980 (Box 133, Folder 21)
  - Oak Ridge Institute of Nuclear Studies, 1963 (Box 133, Folder 22)
  - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, 1963 (Box 133, Folder 23)
  - Old Authors Farm, 1969-1977 (Box 133, Folder 24)
  - Old Dominion College, 1966 (Box 133, Folder 25)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1965-1970 (Box 133, Folder 26)
  - Office of Grants and Research [at Stephen F. Austin State College], 1968 (Box 133, Folder 27)
  - Office of Science and Technology, 1968 (Box 133, Folder 28)
  - Office of the Secretary of the Treasury, 1968 (Box 133, Folder 29)
  - Ohio State University, 1978 (Box 133, Folder 30)
  - Oklahoma Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1980-1981 (Box 133, Folder 31)
  - Oklahoma Baptist University, 1967-1977 (Box 133, Folder 32)
  - Oklahoma State University, 1964-1974 (Box 133, Folder 33)
  - Oklahoma University, 1966 (Box 133, Folder 34)
  - Olin Foundation, 1963 (Box 133, Folder 35)
  - Olivet Baptist Church, 1968 (Box 133, Folder 36)
  - Opportunities, Unlimited, 1967 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Oral History Association, 1975 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Ouachita Baptist University, 1967-1980 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Our Lady of the Lake College, 1967-1975 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Our Little Miss Pageant, 1971-1976 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Outstanding Educators of America, 1969-1973 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Outstanding Personalities of the South, 1967 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Oxford University, 1965-1974 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - P Cross-Reference Sheets, 1962-1977 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - Palm Beach Atlantic College, 1974-1976 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - Pan American Petroleum Corporation, 1963-1965 (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Park Cities Baptist Church, 1962-1979 (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - Parks and Wildlife Department, 1965-1973 (Box 134, Folder 13)
  - Pastoral Counseling Center of Waco, 1966-1968 (Box 134, Folder 14)
  - Patents, 1966-1969 (Box 134, Folder 15)
  - Paul Quinn College, 1962-1968 (Box 134, Folder 16)
  - Paul Quinn College, 1969-1981 (Box 134, Folder 17)
  - Peace Corps, 1962-1964 (Box 134, Folder 18)
  - Peace Corps, 1965-1967 (Box 134, Folder 19)
  - Penal Code, 1966 (Box 134, Folder 20)
  - Pepperdine University, 1973-1981 (Box 134, Folder 21)
  - Philosophical Society of Texas, 1955-1969 (Box 134, Folder 22)
  - Philosophical Society of Texas, 1972-1977 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Phillips Petroleum Company, 1967-1975 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Playboy Controversy (1 of 16), 1980-1981 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Playboy Controversy (2 of 16), 1980-1981 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Playboy Controversy (3 of 16), 1980-1981 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Playboy Controversy (4 of 16), 1980-1981 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Playboy Controversy (5 of 16), 1980-1981 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Playboy Controversy (6 of 16), 1980-1981 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Playboy Controversy (7 of 16), 1980-1981 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Playboy Controversy (8 of 16), 1980-1981 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Playboy Controversy (9 of 16), 1980-1981 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Playboy Controversy (10 of 16), 1980-1981 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Playboy Controversy (11 of 16), 1980-1981 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Playboy Controversy (12 of 16), 1980-1981 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Playboy Controversy (13 of 16), 1980-1981 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Playboy Controversy (14 of 16), 1980-1981 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Playboy Controversy (15 of 16), 1980-1981 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Playboy Controversy (16 of 16), 1980-1981 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Plymouth Park Baptist Church, 1973 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Poetry Society of Texas, 1972-1976 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Polio, 1962 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Political Action Committee of Texans (PACT), 1974 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Politics, 1962-1968 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Prayer Amendment, 1971 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - Precision Engineering Company, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Providence Hospital, 1968 (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - Prudential Insurance Company of America, 1967-1977 (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - Public Health Grant, 1963 (Box 137, Folder 14)
  - Pui Ching Middle School, 1972 (Box 137, Folder 15)
  - Pure Milk Company, 1959-1960 (Box 137, Folder 16)
  - Questionnaires, 1966-1969 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - R Cross Reference Sheets, 1968-1977 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Race Relations, 1960-1968 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Radio Free Europe, 1960-1972 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Radio and Television Commission of the Southern Baptist Convention, 1967-1979 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Radio/Television UT, 1962-1966 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Reagan-Bush Campaign, 1980 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Reagan Education Task Force, 1980 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Regents’ Park College, 1967-1974 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Region XII Education Service Center, 1967-1970 (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Republic National Life Insurance Company, 1964-1969 (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - Republican National Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - Republican Party of Texas, 1960-1977 (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - Research Corporation, 1959-1976 (Box 138, Folder 14)
  - Rhodes Scholarship, 1961-1975 (Box 138, Folder 15)
  - Rice University, 1963-1980 (Box 138, Folder 16)